http://www.schoolmasters.com/pages/privacy

Contact Us : 1 (800) 521-2832
Apparel & ID
ANSI Class 2 ProductsANSI Class 3 ProductsANSI Class E ProductsArmbandsButtonsGlovesHats & CapsHelmetsJacketsPants (Reflective)PinniesRainwearSafety Patrol BeltsSafety VestsSlip-Over CapesT-ShirtsWinter Apparel & AccessoriesWomen's Fitted Safety ApparelCustom ScreeningCrowd Control
Barrier/Caution TapeExpandable BarricadesPennant StreamersPlastic ChainRetractable Cone BarsRope PostsStanchions - AluminumStanchions - PlasticStanchions - SteelCones & Barrels
Commander Traffic DrumsCone AccessoriesCone CartsFlag ConesLighted and Reflective ConesMessage ConesPoly ConesTraffic ConesWatchtower Stacker ConesSafety Patrol
AwardsButtonsSafety Patrol BeltsSigns
Aluminum Traffic Signs (Regular)Aluminum Traffic Signs (Reflective)Cone Top Sign Holder & Street Sign SetsCrosswalk SignsFloor & Sidewalk SignsImpact Recovery System SignsMaintenance SignsPaddle & Wand SignsReversible SignsSign Posts & BasesSnap-On Cone SignsSteel Sign HolderStop SignsVinyl Cone Signs w/ ConeWet Floor Signs & ConesTraffic Control
BarricadesFlag ConesGemstone™ Vertical PanelsHand Held FlagsNavicade™ ChannelizersParking Lot MaintenanceSecurity GatesSpeed Bumps/HumpsStorage
Cooler TransportsCone CartsTotes & ContainersWhistles & Lanyards
AccessoriesElectronic WhistlesLanyardsWhistlesMisc. Equipment
BackpacksBatteriesEye ProtectionFire SafetyFirst AidFlashlights & Light BatonsFloor MatsFloor MarkingGraffiti RemoverMegaphonesNoise ControlSecurity MirrorsWalking RopesScience
AstronomyBiologyBooksBotanyBunsen BurnersChemistryDissecting Kits & SpecimensDVDsEarth ScienceElectricityGlassware / PlasticwareK'Nex Technology KitsLab EquipmentLab Stands & AccessoriesLab ToolsLab Trays & Test Tube RacksLife ScienceLight & ColorMicroscopesMagnetismMagnifiersPhysicsPorcelainRoboticsScience FairSound & WavesSTEMThames & Kosmos Science KitsThermometersWeather & Climate
Fast Order X
Name / Product Code
Qty
Price
Action
Products test
product test
add
+Add all to Cart
School-Tech Inc. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.
What this Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy covers School-Tech's treatment of personally identifiable information that School-Tech Inc. collects when you place an order on our site. This policy also covers School-Tech's treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us.
Information Collection and Use
School-Tech Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you place an order. We may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.
When you place an order, we ask for your name, mailing address, email address and credit card information.
School-Tech Inc. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested.
School-Tech Inc. uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
School-Tech Inc. will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. School-Tech Inc. will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
We have your consent to share the information;
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of School-Tech Inc. to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
School-Tech Inc. may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
Subscribe to our newsletter
A short sentence describing what someone will receive by subscribing
Your email
Subscribe
100% free, Unsubscribe any time!
